<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- edited with XMLSPY v2004 rel. 2 U (http://www.xmlspy.com) by Ed Beach (Firaxis Games) -->
<GameData>
	<LocalizedText>

		<Row Tag="LOC_VICTORY_RICHES_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Riches Victory</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_VICTORY_RICHES_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Earn and stockpile a set amount of gold over the course of the game. Gold can be earned through any means, including trade, pillaging, clearing barbarian outposts, and deals. Gold spent is NOT counted against you for earnings. Victory values are NOT affected by game speed.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_VICTORY_RICHES_EARNINGS_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Earnings</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_VICTORY_RICHES_EARNINGS_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>How much gold must be earned in order to win the game. Set to a low value if you wish to only consider the stockpile option.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_VICTORY_RICHES_STOCKPILE_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Stockpile</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_VICTORY_RICHES_STOCKPILE_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>How much gold must be stockpiled in order to win the game. Set to a low value if you wish to only consider the earnings option.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_VICTORY_RICHES_TEXT" Language="en_US">
			<Text>For what greater purpose does civilization serve than to work together to produce value where there was once none? Through your planning, cunning, specialization of labor, and efforts, you have brought riches to this once basic world. </Text>
		</Row>


		

		<Row Tag="LOC_VICTORY_CHARISMA_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Charisma Victory</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_VICTORY_CHARISMA_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Earn a set amount of great people over the course of the game. Great Prophets and Comandante Generals are not counted towards this goal.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_VICTORY_CHARISMA_PEOPLE_REQ_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Recruitments</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_VICTORY_CHARISMA_PEOPLE_REQ_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>How many great people must be earned to achieve this victory. Without mods, there are 188 great people applicable towards this goal.</Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="LOC_VICTORY_CHARISMA_TEXT" Language="en_US">
			<Text>It is not the nation that lives on in history, but the people that define it. Among our ranks stand the boldest and brightest, drawn to us by a leader who will surely go down as the most charasmatic of all time.</Text>
		</Row>



		<Row Tag="LOC_VICTORY_JOYOUS_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Joyous Victory</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_VICTORY_JOYOUS_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Have the highest [Icon_Amenities] amenity to [Icon_Citizen] population ratio for both a set number of turns, and as a continous streak. Victory values are NOT affected by game speed.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_VICTORY_JOYOUS_TOTAL_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Total</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_VICTORY_JOYOUS_TOTAL_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>How many total turns you must have the highest [Icon_Amenities] amenity to [Icon_Citizen] population ratio in your empire. Set to a low value if you wish to only consider the streak option.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_VICTORY_JOYOUS_CONCURRENT_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Streak</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_VICTORY_JOYOUS_CONCURRENT_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>How many turns in a row you must have the highest [Icon_Amenities] amenity to [Icon_Citizen] population ratio in your empire. Set to a low value if you wish to only consider the total option.</Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="LOC_VICTORY_JOYOUS_TEXT" Language="en_US">
			<Text>A nation is not its culture, nor its military, nor its accomplishments. A nation is its people, and you have ensured that ours are the happiest in the world, regardless of what others may have achieved at the neglect of their own citizens. </Text>
		</Row>
		
		
		
		
		
		
		
		
		
		
		
		
		
		
		
		
		
	</LocalizedText>
</GameData>
